http://songsofpraise.org/privacy.htm

Login or register to interact with other users or receive newsletters.
Plays
Resurrection Song (Easter)
The Perfect Gift (Christmas)
Image Permissions
Misc.
Order
Take care in these dangerous times and reach out to the ones you love
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate his firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
Songs of Praise
Songs of Praise is not a company.
It is not even a registered non-profit organization.
It is an informal affiliation of songwriters and other Christians
who work together to create the content you see and hear.
All inquiries about Songs of Praise should be
directed to
Elton Smith.
This privacy
statement was created so that you will have better information about how your personal information is
stored and used at this site.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information
about the user. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, Google Adsense).
We have no access to or control over these advertising cookies.
In addition, some cookies are generated by the web site itself.
These cookies are used to enable advanced functionality.
For example, they are used to
prevent excessive voting for songs, and to allow a user to note their favorite songs.
You may choose to turn off cookies in your browser.
This site will still work for the most part,
though some features will not be active.
Advertisers
This site uses outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies,
and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, etc.
Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Use of Log Files
Like most web sites, this site uses log files. These log files store internet
protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP),
referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to
analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate,
and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc.
are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Community
You may register with this site and share information about yourself with other visitors.
How much you choose to share is entirely up to you.
Opt-in Newsletter
This site's registration feature contains an opt-in newsletter subscription.
The only information
you are required to provide to receive the newsletter is your email address.
You can unsubscribe at any time to this newsletter.
Use of Your Personal Data
Personal information you provide to this site will NEVER be distributed to third parties
without your prior consent.
External Links
This site contains links to hundreds of other sites.
Care has been made to link only to clean, useful sites, but content is constantly changing and this site cannot
be held responsible for the privacy practices or content of these linked sites.
Please protect your family from the dangers of the internet.
Never leave a child unattended with
free access to the internet.
It is very easy to find dangerous content.
Credit Card Processing
This site uses Paypal for credit card processing.
All credit card numbers are stored in Paypal and cannot be accessed by the site owner.
Please, never send your credit card number in an unsecure email.
It is not safe and this site cannot process your payment this way.
Content Rating
This site is labelled with ICRA.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact:
Elton Smith
Over 400 songs in 17 languages. Four musicals.
Over 700 images.
Everything is freely available for non-profit use.
The latest songs
Tangled Up In The BluesOn Days Like ThisI Believe In The Greatest LoveI Will Listen To YouStill My HeartWaves of SorrowThe Son of ManWhat You've Done For MeSeeking YouMy Jesus I Love TheeAll My Hope Is Found In YouAt Just The Right TimeFather Forgive ThemBecause Of MeIt's ChristmasDaughterMore Than Ever BeforeJesus LivesOnce AgainDraw NearTeach Me Your WayHe Is RisenSan Antonio ChristmasYou Are The OneI Came To ServeAngels SongWhat If Love?Lord Is It Mine?RealizeIt’s A See You LaterYour Presence Is All I NeedA Call To WorshipCome To JesusNow I Find Your PeaceThe Joy Of LifeIn My GardenDelight Yourself In The LordIt's Christmas MornTo The Cross My Heart ReturnsA Christmas PrayerThat's How You Know It's ChristmasSoftly, SweetlyA Child Is BornAs Our Hearts To Heaven CrySpirit Of The Living GodGod Is CallingHe AroseSong For HeleneI Thank You For Your PromisesFinding JoyJesus You're The OneYou Alone Are WorthyMore GraceCounted As One Who Is CleanThe Lord's PrayerOpen ArmsFather I Love YouKing Of The UniverseGlorifyHoly, Humble and ObedientYou Are The ImageLord I Lift Your Name On HighGentle RainYour Beauty Amazes MeMy CrossLive For TodayJoy Is Found In YouI Gave My LifeYou Love Me StillJesus All My Life I Give To You
more...
Copyright © 1996-2020 Elton Smith
